Get out of his life already, will you?
Ruka-chan
LIVE Audio...
Then Haruka was like,
"Did somethin' get ta yer head?!"
And I was like, "Why the
sudden Fukuoka accent?"
Exercise
Heh. Wow.
Kazuya-kun, are you feeling
down about something?
Huh? N-No, nothing like that.
I'm sorry about the other day.
Ex or not, she's your classmate.
I ignored the college implications
and said all sorts of rude things
to your friend in a fit of rage.
Ruka-chan...
Oh, don't worry about it.
Shit was awkward between us anyway.
But you got one thing wrong.
Mami-chan really doesn't
have any feelings for me.
Kazuya-kun...
And I bet she totally hates me now.
Hearing you go so far for me
actually helped me get over it.
Well, don't worry.
I won't let you feel lonely.
I just sent you a cute selfie.
Uh, that's not really
what I was talking about.
Either way, I'm glad
Ruka-chan's back to normal.
Wanna switch to chatting on PC?
I have time tonight.
I could go two hours easily.
Nah, I'm good.
I followed you! ^_^
I'm interested in learning more about sake, and I'm looking forward to seeing fun tweets about your grandson! ^_^
Mizuhara Free
Mizuhara said she was
free on May 20, I think?
It's been a while since I rented
her out, so I'm getting nervous.
fidget fidget
I love you, Kazuya-kun!
I picked this pretty
flower for you.
She has never
said this.
But in the end, I always have
fun because she's so nice.
That's how the rental GF business gets you.
Huh? Mizuhara's not in the usual place.
Rookie Batch
Regular Class
Mizuhara went up a rank!
I see. She's been a rental
girlfriend for more than a year.
Ohhhhhh!
She's not a rookie anymore.
Cast Rank
Regular
Fee
yen / hour
Oh, the hourly fee goes up by a
thousand for regular class, huh?
Well, I can live with a thousand more.
It'll help Mizuhara.
Mizuhara's the only one for me, after all!
Misplaced
Determination
If you like her
Book a date
Wait a sec.
A thousand yen, huh?
You know, couldn't I stand
to be a little more greedy?
I'm paying up as usual, and I'm not asking
her to meet my family or anything.
It's a regular date booking.
Just being with
Mizuhara is enough
to make me happy.
We've usually just gone to cafés, shopped,
and gone to the aquarium at most.
Always perfectly normal date plans.
*If you have any other requests, such as
for specific outfits, please let us know!!
But the service allows for
all kinds of requests,
such as packed lunches and stuff.
I-I mean, you know?
She's probably grown tired
of our usual dates, too.
We're a couple, after all.
Not a
couple.
Monotony is not good.
Self-Justification
Yeah, yeah.
Weekly Shonen Magazine
That said, what can I...
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Oh, God!
I clearly
pushed my
luck!!!
I really went and did it!
Gah! I hope she isn't weirded out!
Will she really show up?
Got it.
I couldn't figure out how
she felt from the text...
Her reply was casual, but maybe
she found it creepy as hell.
But... I regret nothing.
Sorry, I can't go out with you.
Gah
Kibe
I have a boyfriend.
Gah!!
I put my shame aside and asked for this.
I've wanted it since I was in high school.
It's a fantasy that all of mankind wants
to live out once in their lifetimes!
Oh, there you are.
Ba-dump
"Youth and Girlfriend"
Hey.
Maybe we should've picked
a less crowded spot.
ba-dump
fidget
Let's go.
Y-Yeah.
You're really okay with this, huh?
Huh?
I just thought you'd find
it creepy or something.
Well, I do get some clients who want to go
on a date with a girl in school uniform.
What, really?
Damn those freaks.
But why are you in uniform, too?
I-I figured it'd be better this way.
Well, at least we won't look
like schoolgirl and sugar daddy.
Anyway, it's started.
I guess I can still pull
off schoolgirl roles.
A school uniform date with Mizuhara.
Am I really gonna survive this?
Hype levels rising
Tokyo Dome City really is popular.
Even on a weekday, it's packed.
Are all the students here skipping class?
Well, at least they're having fun.
Anyway, what's the plan?
H-Huh?!
Aren't you staring a little too much?
B-Busted!
You're the one who asked me to wear this.
If you say it looks weird, I'll get mad.
I-I would never!
Y-You look great.
I appreciate the flattery.
Let's check out the guide map.
I was being sincere, though...
Holy crap! Mizuhara x School Uniform
is a far deadlier combo than I thought!
That short skirt, the kind she usually
never wears while on rental dates!
Her assertive chest, which that
tight blazer can't cover up!
Her long black hair ties it all together
perfectly. A sum bigger than its parts!
Sparkle
A chain reaction of loveliness!
ba-dump
She's out to destroy all sense of reason!
Want to go a little further in?
H-Huh?!
ba-dump
But I won't back down today.
I'm a client, and I've got
her all to myself today.
She is, without a doubt,
my girlfriend right now.
I made up my mind to be greedier!
I'm gonna turn back time here today
and relive the youth that I lost!
This is a
memorial service...
Farewell,
my youth...
What are you doing? Let's get going.
Why so
pumped up?
I wanna hold hands!
Dream Date Plan Part 1.
A hand-holding date in TDC.
Huh? Hold hands?
I've wanted this ever since the one
time I came here in an all-guy group,
and we spent a hellish time
surrounded by couples everywhere.
But I've never asked her
to hold hands before.
Stare
And I've made my feelings for her obvious
by asking her to be herself on dates.
Here.
It's not
that big
a deal...
Hey! You don't have to pull!
I'm not going anywhere.
M-My bad.
Yikes. I got too worked up.
What a babe! What uniform is that?
I didn't know a girl like that
went to school around here.
I envy her boyfriend so much!
He sure is a dweeb, though.
I wanted my teenage years
to be like that, too.
He's winning at life.
It's begun.
My youth has begun, right here, right now!
For starters, hand-holding cleared.
Next up is...
This! Food sharing!
Lovey-dovey
Another thing all couples do!
Halfsies with Mizuhara would
be a dream come true!
W-Wanna get some churros?
I don't mind, but are you hungry?
Well, it's a TDC thing to do.
I'll go with chocolate, then.
One chocolate, please.
You're not getting any?
Oh, nah, I'm good.
Just me? Are you sure?
O-Of course.
Ugh! I went and bought one,
but I can't ask for a bite!
Here, darling. Say "ahh."
Ahh.
Do you want a bite?
A bite? Can I?
I feel bad eating by myself.
Th-Thanks.
D-Does... Does she know?
What?
Oh, iz nohing.
So close!
Cute! Yummy!
This is good!
I could die... I could die happy now!
Maybe I should get one after all.
What the heck?
Notes
Date Pla
Friday
Date Plan 2
Date Plan 3
Friday
Date Plan 4
What's next on the plan?
So, what next?
You have more things you want to do, right?
Yeah, she does know!
So she did all that for me just now!
You don't have to hide it.
It's not like thinking up
a date plan is a bad thing.
Don't hold back.
I'll go along with whatever today.
Mizuhara...
She may be her usual self,
but she's still a pro.
I did wear this
school uniform and all...
Well, I heard the lady.
I'd be a colossal idiot
if I held back after that.
I'll make this a date I will never forget!
Wha? Sumi-chan?!
Dazed
Rent-a-Girlfriend
fidget
What? What's going on?
Shh! Look over there!
Cute♥
Wha?
Sumi-chan?!
Okay, but why hide?
Look at how we're dressed!
It'd be embarrassing!
True. It would be, a little.
Plus, knowing Sumi-chan,
if she ran into us on a school uniform date,
she might freak out and cause a disaster.
Oh, no! She's coming this way!
Hey, wait!
This angle is dangerous!
Now!
Run for it!
Eep! This is a crisis in more ways than one!
We should be fine here.
She seemed to be looking at men's hats.
A present for her father, maybe?
We practically fled into this arcade,
but that works out for me!
Mizuhara Dream Date Plan
Part 3. Photo booth!
A staple of school uniform dates.
A sanctuary for modern couples,
synonymous with teenage romance!
And it's today's main event!
Because... you get to take it home!
Rumble...
I don't have any pics with Mizuhara.
Getting to feast my eyes on her even at
home would be the wildest dream come true!
Rumble...
Why does popcorn in arcades look so good?
I want it so bad!
W-Wanna take some pics in the photo booth?
Yeah, sure.
That was easy!
Photo booths suddenly give you alone
time, which is bad for the heart.
Do you have any specific kinds
of pics you want to take?
Nah, just the normal stuff.
Okay, choose your plan!
Friends
Couple
Group
Uh, which do I choose?
Three... two...
Uh-oh!
Friends
Couple
Group
We're a couple right now. Don't hold back.
R-Right.
Th-That's right! What was I wimping out for?!
It's time to make my dreams come true!
First, make a heart with your hands.
The kind of smile
that'll make him
want to die
when he looks at it.
Next, hold hands all lovey-dovey!
The kind of smile
he could never
show his parents.
Next, snuggle up and look close!
Can't even be called
a smile anymore.
Oh, man, Mizuhara's hair smells so nice.
Next, face each other and hug!
What?!
Hug? From the front?!
Go on and hug!
Wub you!
*Be sure to hug from the front.
Okay, this is too much.
Come on.
I-Is she sure?!
Hurry it up. Everybody hugs.
It's not a big deal unless you
get all worked up about it.
Don't get the wrong idea, Kazuya!
Mizuhara's just doing her job as a pro!
She's being natural,
Soft
but she's also being a "girlfriend."
It makes all this feel so much more real.
Taking the pic now! Three...
This isn't Mizuhara!
It's a mannequin!
Two...
I can't look her in the face!
One...
Wow, she's totally unperturbed.
I feel so dumb for getting
worked up by myself.
Lastly, heat things up
with a passionate kiss!
Hold on a damn second!
No way, not happening!
"Passionate kiss," my ass! I wish!
This has gotta be too much for Mizuhara...
Come on.
O-Okay.
Three.
Two.
Mwah♥
What a mwahvelous dodge.
School Uniform Date ♥
Kazuya
Chizuru
On the double!!
Come on, come on, come on!
Now I can feast my eyes on Mizuhara
at home every day! I'm in heaven!
Wh-What's up?
Another sudden heart attack moment?
Look!
Wha? The same uniform as Mizuhara's?
C-Current students?!
There's no mistaking it.
They're from Asu North!
I requested it,
so I feel bad.
Mizuhara's cosplaying,
so it'd be all kinds of awkward
if they ran into each other.
Ugh! They're coming this way!
Sorry, let's leave!
School uniform dates bring
so much unexpected trouble.
Sorry I made you run.
Have you
lost weight?
Dead
Oh, no problem.
Mental Kazuya
(brat)
I want that
Mizuhara SSR!!!
This sucks!!!
I really feel like I'm missing out, though.
I'm gonna go get it!
Don't stop me!!!
This sucks!
I want it!
Say, why don't we ride that?
We won't have to worry about
anyone finding us up there,
and we can get some rest.
O-Okay.
Th-This is Dream Date Plan Part 4!
Romantic time on the Ferris wheel!
Diamond doesn't allow closed rooms,
but this is the exception.
It's the perfect way to wrap up a date!
What was that photo for?
That uniform is your own, huh?
I looked online, but...
You learn to appreciate your parents when
you realize how expensive uniforms are.
Damn. That's some real talk.
Holy crap!
Dream come true it may be,
but this is making me so nervous!
Like, I'm alone in a tiny
space with this S-tier beauty?
Where am I supposed to look?
Crap, I clammed up.
Did you know?
The world's first Ferris wheel
could carry 60 people per car.
W-Wow.
She brought this up because
she noticed I'd clammed up.
Come to think of it, every time the
convo was about to die out today,
she kept trying to keep it going.
It had 36 cars, so 2,000 people could
ride at once. Isn't that amazing?
I keep saying she can act natural,
but she's too much of a pro to do so.
Oh, there's a concert happening.
What? Where?
Over there, look. Directly below.
There.
Th-Thanks.
Wh-Where?
Directly below us.
There, at the event space.
Yikes.
We're up close and personal...
Mizuhara's right there...
Huh? Where? I can't see it.
Aw, we don't have a good angle now.
I gotta avoid touching her!
Sorry, I didn't mean to hit you.
No, I should be the one apologizing.
I lost my balance.
What are you doing, idiot?!
Sure, I lost my balance,
but falling on her wasn't on purpose!
Also, wait, my right hand grabbed
something round just now...
It's just me. I'm just imagining it.
A-Anyway, I gotta change the topic.
Th-Thanks for today.
Being a rental girlfriend must be rough.
You have to play along with
your client's requests and all.
Have you never run into trouble?
With creeps and stuff, I mean.
Hmm... I don't think so.
The clients are surprisingly gentlemanly.
I-I see.
Oh, but this one time...
Something happened?
He said he wanted to show
me a picture he really liked
Censored
and whipped out his phone, but
there was porn-y stuff on screen.
Bro, you were
watching porn
right before the date?
Ow, ow, ow!
Today you,
tomorrow me.
That was kind of awkward.
How'd you deal with it?
Pretended I didn't see it, obviously.
It was only for a moment.
Oh... Yeah, you sure have it rough.
What else... Oh, I got yelled at
this one time at the aquarium.
Sarcasm
I'm so sorry
about back then!!
I'm hooked.
I'm in love.
I get to meet all kinds of people and learn,
and go to all kinds of places
and have so many experiences.
She meant with the rental girlfriend job?
When guys who were timid and
couldn't hold a conversation at first
get more and more talkative
and tell me they got a girlfriend,
it kind of makes me happy, too.
Mizuhara...
All I can do is pretend,
but when I learn that even that
lie can bring happiness to people,
it's such a fulfilling moment.
Sometimes I think it's similar to
my acting work... or maybe not.
Shoot. I got all corny there.
You really are amazing.
I'm too loose with my acting mode turned off.
You're always so positive...
Whoa, you can see the Dome from above.
You're doing what you want to do,
and take pride in your work.
It's making me crave some melon bread.
What I want to do...
Oh, we're here. Let's go.
Miss!
The photo we took by the entrance is ready.
You can get it in a photo
album for just a thousand yen.
A thousand yen is too much.
I-I'll take it!
Can you really afford it?
I'll take it! Please!
Desire Fulfilled
I wouldn't dare say I was
after this all along, but...
B
e
a
m
Well, if you want it so badly,
I won't stop you.
Thank you, TDC!
It's almost time.
We should go.
Y-Yeah.
By the way, I need to tell you something.
It's about that play.
I actually got contacted later by a
different producer who came to watch.
I'm rehearsing with them now.
Really?!
H-Hey, keep it down.
Really.
It's for real. Just calm down.
Mizuhara's gonna be in another play?
I'll come watch it for sure!
Thanks.
We've talked about my acting work before,
so I figured I should let you know.
But there's also that other thing....
What other thing?
You know, how I was going to quit
being a rental girlfriend but didn't?
This next play is a minor one, so it won't
have an immediate effect, but eventually...
Yeah?
You're hurting me.
Oh, sorry.
Relax. Don't be so worried.
I won't up and disappear so suddenly—
It's not that.
You've been working so hard...
I'm just so happy for you!
Stupid.
Mizuhara always gives me my best day ever,
and that day was no different.
My dream date was literally
straight out of my fantasies.
But on the way home,
even I couldn't believe how all I
could think about was Mizuhara's play.
Mizuhara had taken a step
closer to her dream.
Nothing else mattered.
And I started to wonder if I could do
anything for her until that day arrived.
No fair, Chizuru-san!
Where did that come from?
Why are you wearing a school uniform?
The Rent-A-GF character who loves
uniforms and is loved by them
is me, Sarashina Ruka, and only me!
Not satisfied with Kazuya-kun,
you wanna keep the school uniform
title to yourself, too?!
Uh, I requested that...
If you like uniforms that much,
just pick me from the start!
Oh, whatever.
Anyway, next time on Rent-a-Girlfriend:
"Kiss and...
...Girlfriend."
I wanna keep him all to
myself, too, you know.
"Kiss and Girlfriend"